=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد أن أستقيل كل يوم =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
(- Bai Jing, are you insane? - Help!)
(- باي جينغ ، هل أنت مجنون؟ - مساعدة!)
(Are you a freak?)
(هل أنت مهووس؟)
(Nobody likes you.)
(لا أحد يحبك.)
Why am I aching all over?
لماذا أشعر بالألم في كل مكان؟
Do you know how annoying you are?
هل تعرف كم أنت مزعج؟
Why did I have such a nightmare?
لماذا كان لدي مثل هذا الكابوس؟
(Nagger) (Nagger is calling.)
(ناجر) (ناغر ينادي.)
Is the doctor calling to tell me he's dead?
هل يتصل الطبيب ليخبرني أنه مات؟
(Nagger is...)
(Nagger هو ...)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Morning, Secretary Bai.
صباح السكرتير باي.
Boss, you're awake?
رئيس ، هل أنت مستيقظ؟
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
I told all departments the meeting was moved up half an hour.
أخبرت جميع الإدارات أنه تم تأجيل الاجتماع لمدة نصف ساعة.
Within a quarter, pick me up downstairs of my apartment.
في غضون ربع ، اصطحبني من شقتي في الطابق السفلي.
I want two Chinese crepes from...
أريد كريبان صينيان من ...
Wait, wait.
انتظر انتظر.
Why does it sound so familiar?
لماذا يبدو مألوفا جدا؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
What date is it today?
ما هو تاريخ اليوم؟
Are you my secretary or am I yours?
هل أنت سكرتيرتي أم أنا لك؟
Hurry.
عجل.
(May 20, Friday)
(20 مايو ، الجمعة)
(He isn't disabled.)
(هو غير معاق).
(He looks healthy, too.)
(يبدو بصحة جيدة أيضًا).
(He's indeed all right.)
(إنه بخير حقًا).
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Yes.
نعم.
OK, Boss.
حسنا ايها الرئيس.
Boss, your cufflink dropped.
سيدي ، زر الكم الخاص بك انخفض.
(It's the same in my dream.)
(الأمر نفسه في حلمي).
No appetite. I don't want it.
لا شهية.  لا اريدها.
(Oh, no, the elevator.)
(أوه ، لا ، المصعد.)
Boss, the elevator is out of service.
السيد الرئيس ، المصعد خارج الخدمة.
Let's go up the stairs.
دعنا نصعد السلالم.
I'm already in the car.
أنا بالفعل في السيارة.
OK.
نعم.
Be right there.
ساكون هناك.
Out of service?
خارج الخدمة؟
Get out of my way.
ابتعد عن طريقي.
(What's this about?)
(ما هذا؟)
Let's take the stairs.
لنأخذ السلالم.
(I feel I reviewed these files before.)
(أشعر أنني راجعت هذه الملفات من قبل.)
(And the cufflink and elevator.)
(وزرة الكم والمصعد.)
(Why do I feel all those things happened once?)
(لماذا أشعر أن كل هذه الأشياء حدثت مرة واحدة؟)
(I managed to resign.)
(تمكنت من الاستقالة).
(But why is this day repeating again?)
(ولكن لماذا هذا اليوم يتكرر مرة أخرى؟)
(If they really happened before...)
(إذا حدثوا بالفعل من قبل ...)
Secretary Bai...
سكرتيرة باي ...
(Does my resignation have nothing to do with the loop?)
(هل استقالتي لا علاقة لها بالحلقة؟)
(Oh, no!)
(أوه ، لا!)
(Oh, no, I forgot about you.)
(أوه ، لا ، لقد نسيت عنك.)
Bai Jing,
باي جينغ ،
why did you have me fired?
لماذا طردتني
How dare you bully my girl!
كيف تجرؤ على التنمر على فتاتي!
Mr. Jin...
السيد جين ...
Get out!
اخرج!
Don't hurt the image of our company.
لا تؤذي صورة شركتنا.
(I was still late.)
(كنت ما زلت متأخرًا).
(But why did I predict this?)
(لكن لماذا توقعت هذا؟)
Boss,
رئيس،
I should buy noodles for you, huh?
يجب أن أشتري المعكرونة لك ، هاه؟
I'll freshen up
سأنتعش
and go immediately.
وتذهب على الفور.
Why do noodles sound so unpleasant?
لماذا تبدو المعكرونة غير سارة؟
Secretary Bai,
سكرتير باي ،
what will you have for lunch?
ماذا ستأكل على الغداء؟
Me?
أنا؟
(Why doesn't he want noodles today?)
(لماذا لا يريد المعكرونة اليوم؟)
Secretary Bai...
سكرتيرة باي ...
(He doesn't like it?)
(لا يحب ذلك؟)
Boss, spicy hot pot is cheap.
بوس ، وعاء ساخن حار رخيص.
But it has meat and vegetables.
لكنها تحتوي على لحوم وخضروات.
There are many flavors, too.
هناك العديد من النكهات أيضًا.
It's perfect for an employee.
إنه مثالي للموظف.
I just want some chopped scallion.
أريد فقط بعض البصل الأخضر المفروم.
Chopped scallion?
بصل أخضر مقطع؟
OK, OK.
حسنا حسنا.
The taste of the restaurant at University Avenue.
طعم المطعم في شارع الجامعة.
Ms. Zhang's Spicy Hot Pot near the east gate of the university...
حار وعاء السيدة تشانغ بالقرب من البوابة الشرقية للجامعة ...
In the right lane 300 meters away.
في الممر الأيمن 300 متر.
Boss, you also went there before?
رئيس ، هل ذهبت إلى هناك أيضا من قبل؟
It's very popular with college students.
إنها تحظى بشعبية كبيرة بين طلاب الجامعات.
I often eat late there.
كثيرا ما أتناول الطعام في وقت متأخر هناك.
Sectary Bai,
طائفي باي ،
why did you come to our company after graduation?
لماذا أتيت إلى شركتنا بعد التخرج؟
Because
لان
I...
أنا...
Shi'an,
شيآن
you even eat spicy hot pot?
حتى أنك تأكل وعاء ساخن حار؟
Secretary Bai,
سكرتير باي ،
the contract period should be five years.
يجب أن تكون مدة العقد خمس سنوات.
Could you modify it?
هل يمكنك تعديله؟
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Shi'an, tonight...
شيآن ، الليلة ...
Ms. Feng,
السيدة فنغ ،
I know what you're going to say.
أعرف ما ستقوله.
But you'd better not say it.
لكن من الأفضل ألا تقول ذلك.
Because you won't get a satisfactory answer.
لأنك لن تحصل على إجابة مرضية.
And since when could you
ومنذ متى يمكنك ذلك
order my secretary about?
تأمر سكرتيرتي؟
I want to tell you something about the meeting this afternoon.
أريد أن أخبركم بشيء عن الاجتماع بعد ظهر اليوم.
(Meeting?)
(لقاء؟)
Mr. Wang is the actual controller of Kewei Corporation,
السيد وانغ هو المراقب الفعلي لشركة Kewei ،
instead of Mr. Li who has been interacting with us.
بدلاً من السيد "لي" الذي كان يتفاعل معنا.
Mr. Wang has a company of suspected fraudulent activities.
السيد وانغ لديه شركة أنشطة احتيالية مشتبه بها.
Before signing the contract this afternoon,
قبل توقيع العقد بعد ظهر اليوم ،
show me the information about Mr. Wang
أرني المعلومات حول السيد وانغ
with Kewei Corporation.
مع شركة Kewei.
OK.
نعم.
The contract is modified.
تم تعديل العقد.
Where's Ms. Feng?
أين السيدة فنغ؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
And finish your lunch.
وانتهي من غدائك.
The taste hasn't changed at all.
الطعم لم يتغير إطلاقا.
I slipped up in the reference checking.
لقد تعثرت في فحص المرجع.
Mr. Wang is the actual controller of Kewei Corporation,
السيد وانغ هو المراقب الفعلي لشركة Kewei ،
instead of Mr. Li who has been interacting with us.
بدلاً من السيد "لي" الذي كان يتفاعل معنا.
Mr. Wang has a company of suspected fraudulent activities.
السيد وانغ لديه شركة أنشطة احتيالية مشتبه بها.
Let's not sign the contract today.
دعونا لا نوقع العقد اليوم.
Before signing the contract,
قبل توقيع العقد ،
collect the evidence
جمع الأدلة
on their suspected fraudulent activities
بشأن أنشطتهم الاحتيالية المشتبه بها
in case they blame us.
في حالة إلقاء اللوم علينا.
(Weird.)
(عجيب.)
(How did Ms. Feng find out about it before I told her?)
(كيف اكتشفت السيدة فنغ ذلك قبل أن أخبرها؟)
Secretary Bai, tell everyone
السكرتير باي ، أخبر الجميع
that the meeting is canceled.
أن الاجتماع قد تم إلغاؤه.
OK.
نعم.
(All my predictions happened.)
(حدثت كل توقعاتي.)
(Is it because...)
(هل هذا بسبب...)
(Prophecy...)
(نبوءة ...)
(I'm indeed the Chosen One.)
(أنا بالفعل المختار).
=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد أن أستقيل كل يوم =
(The right of communication through network exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(يعود حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة حصريًا إلى Tencent.)